linkinprofile.com 2019-05-04

# Link In Profile

_updated: May 25, 2018_

## Link in Profile Account Privacy Policies

### Scope

This Privacy Policy informs you how we collect and use your data with Link in Profile ("Company" or "We"). Your privacy is super important to us, so we wrote our Privacy Policy so you could understand it. However, if you have any questions, feel free to reach out to our legal team at [legal@linkinprofile.com](mailto:legal@linkinprofile.com). 

### Overview

Link in Profile is designed for you to turn your Instagram followers into your Esty shoppers, blog readers, Shopify customers or website viewers. We do this by linking your Instagram account with our own servers and analyzing the media you post to Instagram. With a Link in Profile account, any media that you post with a URL in the caption will be posted to your Link in Profile landing page. Because of this, your privacy is very important to us. We work extremely hard at all times to maintain your prevent unauthorized access to your data. We think you should control who your data is shared with, not us. To that end, we’ve developed this Privacy Policy to explain to you how we collect, use, disclose, transfer and store your information when you use our service or software. Please take a moment to review this policy and do not hesitate to contact us with any questions via the email address included at the top and bottom of this page.

## What Personal Information Does Link in Profile Collect and Why?

We collect and process the following data about you:

  * **Information that you give us** \- we collect information about you when you register for the Service, when you interact with us online (for example via email) and when you subscribe to the service.
  * **Information we collect about you and your device** \- we automatically collect some information about the devices you use to access the Services in order to provide greater customer support in solving any issues that may arise. 
  * **Information we receive from third parties** \- we automatically ingest information from third parties that you connect with the Services, for example Instagram, and other social networks. That information is governed by their respective Privacy Policies.
  * **Cookies and other similar technologies** \- we use cookies to distinguish you from other users to make the use of our service more enjoyable. 

**_If you create a Link in Profile Account:_**

We May Collect | Why We Collect It  
---|---  
Your email address | We use your email address to: log you in to the App, communicate with you about new features, support items, important account notifications and other marketing related emails. You may always opt out of the marketing emails that we provide if you choose to do so.  
Your name associated with your account | We display the name and title on your public profile for the App and we use the tags to help group users of similar interests so we can better cater to your needs.  
A private access token for Instagram | To access information about your Instagram account, we collect a token that we can then securely make requests on your behalf to Instagram.  
Your Website URL from your Instagram Profile | We will collect the profile address in your Instagram account to be sure we provide the proper customer service to you when you request it. We do this to know if you are using the App or not currently in Instagram.  
The location of where you register | To be sure that the locations being used are covered by our policies and practices.  
The type of device you register with | We collect device information to better serve you in either a support role, or when we release new features to be sure they operate with your device.  
Anonymous logging of our API usage | We monitor API usage to make sure there are no errors and to be sure that the entire system is operating at top efficiency.  
  
**_If you Pay for a Link in Profile Subscription:_**

We Will Collect | Why We Collect It  
---|---  
Your address | In order for our payment provider Stripe to charge cards, we must pass along other information to validate your credit card.  
Your credit card number | In order to charge you for the service, we collect and pass along your credit card information to Stripe. We do not store your credit card information anywhere in our system. We store a reference to that information that we can then interact with Stripe accordingly.  
  
**_If you visit linkinprofile.com or any landing pages:_**

We Will Collect | Why We Collect It  
---|---  
IP address, pages visited, browser type and settings | We are constantly monitoring the use of the App to be sure it is working properly and to also inform you about visits to your Link in Profile should you be on a plan that includes Stats Collection  
  
**_Some of our App Integrations Include:_**

App | Reason for Being  
---|---  
Intercom | To interact with you in a more streamlined fashion for both marketing and support reasons. [Intercom's Privacy Policy](https://www.intercom.com/terms-and-policies#privacy)  
Stripe | To process payment for your account. [Stripe's Privacy Policy](https://stripe.com/us/privacy)  
Google Analytics | To record how you and your followers use the App so we can make it the best possible version of itself. [Google Analytics Privacy Policy ](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=us)  
Postmark | To send you automated emails when your account is in a bad state. [Postmark's Privacy Policy](https://wildbit.com/privacy-policy)  
  
## Marketing

We may use your email address to build out a customer profile for you. We intend for this profile to be beneficial to you as we can better inform you of product features and opportunities that are more targeted as opposed to blasting you with an email any time something new may be of interest. You can always ask us to not inform you of deals or opportunities and we will respect that decision in offering our Service. We DO NOT share your information with unaffiliated third parties.

### Your California Privacy Rights

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the "Shine The Light" law, permits customers who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. We do not share your personal information with unaffiliated third parties for their own marketing purposes, but you are free to request this report. If you are a California resident and would like more information, please submit your request to [legal@linkinprofile.com](mailto:legal@linkinprofile.com) with the subject line "California privacy rights."

## Data Storage, Transfer and Deletion

### How do I Make Changes to My Personal Information?

You can make changes to your personal information by contacting us, or logging into the App and making changes there at any time.

### Where is My Personal Information Stored?

We store your information in our US Data Centers located in the United States of America. 

### How Secure is My Personal Information?

We take many precautions to protect your information through administrative, technical, and physical safeguards to protect the security, confidentiality, and integrity of your personal information. For example, we use industry standard (SSL) encryption to protect your network communications; to the extent allowed by law, we run background checks on our employees; and we architect our networks to protect access to our storage servers. In addition to maintaining our high level of security, we are always striving to increase our security measures.

### How do I Delete My Personal Information Maintained by Link in Profile?

Please reach out to our support team and we will delete your information immediately from our Service. [support@linkinprofile.com](mailto:support@linkinprofile.com)

## Last, but Certainly Not Least

### Children

Our Services are not intended for children under 13 years of age. No one under age 13 may sign up through the Services. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. If you are under 13, do not use or provide any information through the Services or on or through any of their features or register an account, make any purchases through the Services, use any of the interactive features of the Services or provide any information about yourself to us, including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address or any screen name or user name you may use. If we learn we have collected or received personal information from a child under 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under 13, please contact us at [support@linkinprofile.com](mailto:support@linkinprofile.com).

### Notification of Privacy Statement Changes

We may update this privacy statement to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email (sent to the email address specified in your account) or by means of a notice on Link in Profile’s website prior to the change becoming effective. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices.

### Contact Information

If you have any questions or comments in relation to this Privacy Policy, please contact: [legal@linkinprofile.com](mailto:legal@linkinprofile.com).
